[{"questionBody":"Is Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is IETF :improve :Internet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :transmits :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :transmits :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Framing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Framing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Error_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Error_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Extranet :has :VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Extranet :has :VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Extranet :has :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Extranet :has :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Guided_Media :part_of :Communication_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Twisted_Pair :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Twisted_Pair :part_of :Communication_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Twisted_Pair :part_of :Communication_Media","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Guided_Media :part_of :Communication_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Optical_Fibre :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Optical_Fibre :part_of :Communication_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Optical_Fibre :part_of :Communication_Media","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Guided_Media :part_of :Communication_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Coaxial_Cable :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Coaxial_Cable :part_of :Communication_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Coaxial_Cable :part_of :Communication_Media","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ISP :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ISP :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ISP :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Router :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing_table :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Routing_table :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing_table :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ISP :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ISP :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ISP :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing_table :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Routing_table :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing_table :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ISP :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ISP :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ISP :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing_table :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Routing_table :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing_table :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ISP :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ISP :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ISP :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing_table :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Routing_table :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing_table :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ISP :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ISP :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ISP :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing_table :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Routing_table :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing_table :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ISP :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ISP :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ISP :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distance_Vector_Routing :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Static_Routing :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_Routing :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Link_State_Routing :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Broad_Band_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing_table :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Routing_table :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing_table :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Cut_Through :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Fragment_Free :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Adaptive_Switching :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Store_and_Forward :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wifi_Repeater :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :LAN_Repeater :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Routing :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Packet :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Logical_Addressing :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Logical_Addressing :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Logical_Addressing :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Forwarding :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Forwarding :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Forwarding :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Flow_Control :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Flow_Control :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Flow_Control :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Error_Control :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Error_Control :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Error_Control :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Frames :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Frames :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Frames :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Physical_Addressing :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Physical_Addressing :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Physical_Addressing :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Media_Access_Control :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Media_Access_Control :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Media_Access_Control :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Framing :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Framing :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Framing :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Control :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Access_Control :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Control :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Routing :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Packet :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Logical_Addressing :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Logical_Addressing :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Logical_Addressing :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Forwarding :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Forwarding :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Forwarding :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Flow_Control :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Flow_Control :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Flow_Control :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Error_Control :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Error_Control :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Error_Control :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Frames :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Frames :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Frames :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Physical_Addressing :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Physical_Addressing :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Physical_Addressing :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Media_Access_Control :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Media_Access_Control :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Media_Access_Control :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Framing :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Framing :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Framing :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Control :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Access_Control :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Control :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Routing :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Routing :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Packet :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Logical_Addressing :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Logical_Addressing :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Logical_Addressing :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Forwarding :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Forwarding :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Forwarding :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":